Guide to the Sholom Secunda Papers Ca. 1926-1971 MSS 054
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX. Orchestral Arrangements
  - Prokofiev Overture, undated (Box 60)
  - Reb Dovid'l, undated (Box 60)
  - Russian Revolutionary Songs, undated (Box 60)
  - Russian Potpourri, undated (Box 60)
  - Russian Selections, undated (Box 60)
  - Tango, undated (Box 60)
  - Taps, undated (Box 60)
  - Theater Potpourri, undated (Box 61)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061876 4
  - Volga Boat Song, undated (Box 61)
  - What do I care, undated (Box 61)
  - Who Blew Out the Flame, undated (Box 61)
  - Yiddish Medley, undated (Box 61)
- Series X. Arrangements (Folk and Theater)
  - Alle Mentch'n Tantsendig, undated (Box 62)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061877 2
  - Alte Kashe, undated (Box 62)
  - Anniversary Song, undated (Box 62)
  - Arbitering Hymn, undated (Box 62)
  - Belts, undated (Box 62)
  - A Brivele Der Mamen, undated (Box 62)
  - Chassidic Nigun, undated (Box 62)
  - Chasidism, undated (Box 62)
  - Chazend'l Oyf Shabes, undated (Box 62)
  - Ch'ssidish, undated (Box 62)
  - DiMezinke, undated (Box 62)
  - A Din Toyre Mit Gott, undated (Box 62)
  - Dort Vu Di Tseyder, undated (Box 62)
  - A Du Du, undated (Box 63)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061878 0
  - Eyli, Eyli, undated (Box 63)
  - FolkSong Medley, undated (Box 63)
  - Gey Ikh Mir Shpatsir'n, undated (Box 63)
  - GrinehKuzineh, undated (Box 63)
  - Hald Di Festung, undated (Box 63)
  - Ich Mob Dich Tsu Tiel Lieb, undated (Box 63)
  - In Di Hoy'fn, undated (Box 63)
  - In Kheyder, undated (Box 63)
  - Internationale, undated (Box 63)
  - L'koved Dem Haylig'n Shabes, undated (Box 63)
  - May Ko Mash MaLon, undated (Box 63)
  - Makabeer, undated (Box 63)
  - MaynMame, undated (Box 63)
  - Mayn Yiddishe Mame, undated (Box 63)
  - My Hero, undated (Box 63)
  - Oy Mame!, undated (Box 63)
  - Oyf'n Pripitchik, undated (Box 64)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061879 8
  - Oyf'nPripitchik, undated (Box 64)
  - Reyzele, undated (Box 64)
  - Shayn Vi Di Levone, undated (Box 64)
  - Shlof Lid, undated (Box 64)
  - A Shvue, undated (Box 64)
  - If in Veldele, undated (Box 64)
  - Tsig Tsigetsap, undated (Box 64)
  - Ven Ich Volt Geven Der BoireOlom, undated (Box 64)
  - A Yiddish Korentsl, undated (Box 64)
  - Zys Wit Keynmo, undated (Box 64)
- Series XI.Goldfaden Arrangements
  - Solos, Duets, Chorus, undated (Box 65)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061880 6
  - Orchestrations, undated (Box 66)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061881 4
  - Shulamis Ballet, undated (Box 67)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061882 2
  - Shulamis Fantasia, undated (Box 67)
  - AkeydalYitskhok, undated (Box 68)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061883 0
  - Goldfaden Potpourri, undated (Box 68)
  - Veynt Tsion's Tekhter, undated (Box 68)
- Series XII. Published Music (Liturgical and Orchestral)
  - Ad Mosay (Vi Lang Nokh), undated (Box 69)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061884 8
  - AmYisroel Khay, undated (Box 69)
  - Aheym, Aheym, undated (Box 69)
  - Am YisroelKhai, undated (Box 69)
  - Bay Mir Bist Du Sheyn, undated (Box 69)
  - Der Oybershter FunShtoys'l, undated (Box 69)
  - Bist Mayn Zin, undated (Box 69)
  - Chassidisher Nigun, undated (Box 69)
  - Chi-ri-bim, Chi-ri-bom, undated (Box 69)
  - Di Epl Farkoyferen, undated (Box 69)
  - Di Feylst Mir, undated (Box 69)
  - Dona, Dona, undated (Box 69)
  - Dos KleynehShanayderl, undated (Box 69)
  - Dos Yiddishe Lid, undated (Box 69)
  - GanovimAmol Un Haynt, undated (Box 70)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061885 5
  - Heym, Zise Heym, undated (Box 70)
  - Hit AykhMeydlakh, undated (Box 70)
  - Hob Mikh Lib, undated (Box 70)
  - Ikh BeynkNokh A Shmeykh'l, undated (Box 70)
  - Ikh Darf Dikh, undated (Box 70)
  - Ikh HobMayn Harts Farloyrn, undated (Box 70)
  - In Keynem's Land, undated (Box 70)
  - Libe GefintShoyn A Veg, undated (Box 70)
  - Libes Lid, undated (Box 70)
  - Manishcewitz Matzo andKoyft, Koyft, undated (Box 70)
  - Mayn Yiddishe Meydele, undated (Box 70)
  - MyMother's Sabbath Candles, undated (Box 70)
  - Nigun Un Hardolo, undated (Box 70)
  - Nokh A Reg'n Shaynt Di Zin, undated (Box 70)
  - Oo-La-La, undated (Box 70)
  - Oyb S'izBashert, undated (Box 70)
  - Rumania Rumania, undated (Box 70)
  - Sh'ma Koleynu, undated (Box 70)
  - Shtif Mames, undated (Box 70)
  - Shver Tsu Zayn A Yid, undated (Box 70)
  - Slutzk, undated (Box 70)
  - There Is One Lord, undated (Box 70)
  - Ven Ikh Zol Zayn A Shnayder, undated (Box 70)
  - Yiddishe Meydlakh, undated (Box 70)
  - Zing Satil, undated (Box 70)
  - Zing Farvus, undated (Box 70)
  - Liturgical Works, undated (Box 71)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061886 3
  - Orchestral Works, undated (Box 72)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061887 1
  - Orchestral Works, undated (Box 73)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061888 9
- Series XIII. Oratorios
  - Yizkor: In Memory of the Six Million (Manuscript Text), undated (Box 74)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061889 7
  - If Not Higher, undated (Box 75)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061890 5
- Series XIV. Symphonic Poem
  - A Day at a Kibbutz, undated (Box 76)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061891 3
- Series XV. Services
  - Passover, undated (Box 77)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061892 1
  - Passover, undated (Box 78)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061893 9
  - Passover, undated (Box 79)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061894 7
  - Passover, undated (Box 80)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061895 4
  - Yom Kippur, undated (Box 81a.)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061896 2
  - Rhosh Hashona, undated (Box 81b.)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061897 0
  - Simchat Torah, undated (Box 82)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061898 8
  - Chanukah, undated (Box 82)
  - Purim, undated (Box 82)
  - Shabbas, undated (Box 83)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061899 6
  - Shabbas, undated (Box 84)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061900 2
- Series XVI.Miscellaneous (Theater and Film)
  Series XVI contains scores for various theater works and one film, Tevye.
  - Alts Iz Double, undated (Box 85)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061901 0
  - Aria, undated (Box 85)
  - Ballet, undated (Box 85)
  - Bedouin, undated (Box 85)
  - Bukovina, undated (Box 85)
  - Coris, undated (Box 85)
  - Dance, undated (Box 85)
  - Duets (note: did not list individualduets, as not all are named), undated (Box 85)
  - Ensemble, undated (Box 85)
  - Entrances, undated (Box 86)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061902 8
  - Farvos Kumt Es Mir, undated (Box 86)
  - Finale - First Act, undated (Box 86)
  - Finale - Loose Instrumental Parts, undated (Box 86)
  - A Fraynt, undated (Box 86)
  - Funiculi, Funicula, undated (Box 86)
  - Gedeynk! Ikh Hob Mayn HartsGegeb'n Dir, undated (Box 86)
  - Goldene Khasene, undated (Box 86)
  - Herring MitPotatoes, undated (Box 86)
  - Ikh Bin Farlibt, undated (Box 86)
  - I Would If I Could, undated (Box 86)
  - Kiddush, undated (Box 86)
  - Khasene, undated (Box 86)
  - Ma Tovu, undated (Box 86)
  - Mazurka, undated (Box 86)
  - M'Hot Mikh Nit Arayn Gelost, undated (Box 86)
  - Moyshe, undated (Box 86)
  - Nadir Mayns, undated (Box 86)
  - Odom in Khave, undated (Box 86)
  - Opening Acts (First and Second), undated (Box 86)
  - Orchestration Parts, undated (Box 86)
  - Oy, Siz A Mechaye, undated (Box 86)
  - Oy, Vey Iz Tsu Mir, undated (Box 86)
  - Piano Parts, undated (Box 86)
  - Polka, undated (Box 87)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061903 6
  - Prelude Parts, undated (Box 87)
  - Quartet, undated (Box 87)
  - Rio rio, undated (Box 87)
  - Salutations, undated (Box 87)
  - Sashre, undated (Box 87)
  - S'geyr Nit, undated (Box 87)
  - S'izAndere Tsayt'n, undated (Box 87)
  - S'iz Unzer Heym, undated (Box 87)
  - Show Parts, undated (Box 87)
  - Tel Aviv, undated (Box 87)
  - Tevye [Film], undated (Box 92)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061907 7
  - Trios, undated (Box 87)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 87)
  - Vocal Music, undated (Box 87)
  - Vu Nemt Men Di Libe, undated (Box 87)
  - Waltz, undated (Box 87)
  - Whoopee, undated (Box 87)
  - YomHaatsmaut, undated (Box 87)
  - Zayn Fargesene Gelibte, undated (Box 87)
  - Zi Hot MichOysgelakht, undated (Box 87)
  - Proclaim Liberty (Pageant), undated (Box 88)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061904 4
  - TheWorld, undated (Box 89)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061905 1
  - Unidentified Theater Music, undated (Box 90)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061906 9
  - ConcertFreylakhs (Original Orchestral), undated (Box 91a.)
  - Shabbat Shalom (Original Vocal), undated (Box 91a.)
  - Lord Will Rebuild, undated (Box 91a.)
  - Tzena, Tzena, undated (Box 91a.)
  - Bel Mir, undated (Box 91.b)
  - Faith Alone, undated (Box 91.b)
  - Ch'sidish, undated (Box 91.b)
  - A day in a Kibbutz, undated (Box 91.b)
  - Concert Frelakhs, undated (Box 91.b)
- Series XVII.Photographs
  - Secunda with notables (Ben Gurion, Casals, Tibbet, Peerce, etc), undated (Box 93)
  - Secunda with Richart Tucker, undated (Box 93)
  - ConcordHotel Years, undated (Box 93)
  - Bay Mir Bist Du Sheyn, undated (Box 93)
  - Professional, undated (Box 94)
  - Professional Groups, undated (Box 94)
  - Head Shots, undated (Box 94)
  - Contact Sheets (Publicity Kits), undated (Box 94)
  - Sholom and Hymie Jacobson(1923) (Box 94)
  - Sholom and Betty, undated (Box 95)
  - Betty, undated (Box 95)
  - Sholom, undated (Box 95)
  - Scanned, undated (Box 95)
  - Mixed Groupings - Family,Organizations, and Performances, undated (Box 96)
  - Mostly Sheldon, undated (Box 96)
  - Travel/Tours, undated (Box 97)
  - Miscellaneous family and friends, undated (Box 97)
  - FamilyGroup, undated (Box 97)
  - Sheldon and Eugene, undated (Box 97)
- Series XVIII. Secunda's Belongings
  - NewspaperClippings, undated (Box 98-99)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061908 5/ 3 1142 04061909 3
  - Di Tsukunft (Yiddish Monthly, 1924) (Box 98-99)
  - Personal Papers, undated (Box 98-99)
  - Programs, undated (Box 98-99)
  - Scripts/Lyrics: To songs, the film "Tevye", undated (Box 98-99)
  - Translation of note (about"The Song of Love"), undated (Box 98-99)
  - Abi Gezunt, undated (Box 100)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061910 1
  - Adama, undated (Box 100)
  - Al Tashlicheinu, undated (Box 100)
  - An Eybiger Tants, undated (Box 100)
  - Anthem of the U.S.S.R, undated (Box 100)
  - Az Ikh volt Geven Der, undated (Box 100)
  - Crazy Rhythm, undated (Box 100)
  - Di Grine Kuzine, undated (Box 100)
  - DiShuve, undated (Box 100)
  - Dos Butcher'l, undated (Box 100)
  - Dos Sheyfele, undated (Box 100)
  - Dos Tsigayner Meyd'l, undated (Box 100)
  - Del Choclo, undated (Box 100)
  - (A)Dudele, undated (Box 100)
  - Es Feylt Ir Di Rozhinke, undated (Box 100)
  - Farblondzhet in DiViste, undated (Box 100)
  - Fuch, undated (Box 100)
  - A Grus Fun Der Heym, undated (Box 100)
  - Kreitzberg Songs, undated (Box 100)
  - Ikh Vil Zikh Shpilen, undated (Box 100)
  - Internationale, undated (Box 100)
  - Mai-Ko-Mashma-Lon, undated (Box 100)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 100)
  - Papa Tree, undated (Box 100)
  - Partizane, undated (Box 100)
  - Proch, undated (Box 100)
  - Regend'l, undated (Box 100)
  - Sing, Sing, Sing, undated (Box 100)
  - Tango Argention, undated (Box 100)
  - Tsu Dir Maun Land - Amerika, undated (Box 100)
  - Vos Geven iz Geven Un Nito, undated (Box 100)
- Series XIX. Correspondence
  - Correspondence, 1926-1971 (Box 101)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061911 9
  - Correspondence, 1926-1971 (Box 102)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061912 7
- Series XX. Sound Recordings (Acetates and Commercial)
  Use Restrictions
  Access copies for sound recordings may not be available to researchers. Please contact a Fales archivist for access questions.
  - LP's, undated (Box 103-105)
  - Cassettes, undated (Box 106)
  - Acetates, undated (Box 107-108)
  - Magnetic Reels, undated (Box 109)
- Series XXI.Related Materials
  - Shol Biography Translations, undated (Box 110)
  - Shol Music, undated (Box 110)
  - SecundaMusic Collection, undated (Box 110)
  - Chapter Notes for Victoria Secunda's Biograpy ofSholom Secunda, undated (Box 111)